{
    "subject": "resource/Stockdale_High_School_(Bakersfield,_California)",
    "predicate": "property/principal",
    "object": "Ramon Hendrix",
    "human_readable": "The principal of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California) is Ramon Hendrix.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644476175308228,
            "question": "Name the principal of Stockdale High School."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9266022443771362,
            "question": "Is Ramon Hendrix a teacher at Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9207533597946167,
            "question": "Who is the principal of Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.774963915348053,
            "question": "Does Stockdale High School exist in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7409113049507141,
            "question": "In what state is Stockdale High School situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7299335598945618,
            "question": "What is the name of the high school that Ramon Hendrix leads?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7283106446266174,
            "question": "Where is Stockdale High School located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6271153092384338,
            "question": "What is Ramon Hendrix's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5997409820556641,
            "question": "Where does Ramon Hendrix work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5667200088500977,
            "question": "What city is home to Stockdale High School?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The principal of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California) is Ramon Hendrix.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2456_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Ramon Hendrix work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2456_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ramon Hendrix's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2456_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Stockdale High School located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2456_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2456_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, it is stated that \"Ramon Hendrix, Principal\" is part of the faculty and staff list for Stockdale High School in Bakersfield, California. This directly supports the query stating that Ramon Hendrix is the principal of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions two different Stockdale High Schools, one in Bakersfield, California, and the other in Stockdale, Texas. The principal mentioned for the Texas school is Sandra Lynn, but it does not provide any information about the principal of the Bakersfield, California school, which implies that Ramon Hendrix is the principal of the Stockdale High School in Texas, not the one in Bakersfield, California.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}